Open the ProduceFiles folder and find the C.AligningShoulderSims file in the FindTuning folder.
In the T-ShirtAligningShoulderSims file, drag it to the 3D or 2D window.
Press the 5 on the keyboard to switch to the top view.
In the 3D tool bar, select the surface length measurement virtual model tool on the virtual model tool.
Start creating a virtual tape, with the orange dots moving along the mouse cursor.
Press once along the shoulder line at the height of the shoulder, and then point the mouse cursor to the point.
The double-click has completed the virtual tape production.
In the 3D tool bar, click on the left-click on the virtual model tape tool.
Select the 3D model measurement tool.
Click on the 3D clothing line.
The bar becomes transparent.
Then click on the virtual measurement created earlier.
The two lines are shown in red.
The 3D clothing line will move and stick to the virtual model measurement line.
In the 3D tool bar, select the move tool.
If the T-shirt line is far from the actual line, the clothing will shake sharply and may cause the wear effect to be unfavorable.
In the simulated state, gently pull the clothing until it fits the virtual model.
In the 3D tool bar, select the improve clothing quality tool.
In the 3D tool bar, click OK.
Activate the simulation.
In the 3D tool bar, select the edit measurement virtual model tool.
According to the need to rotate the virtual model, you can clearly see the virtual measurement on the shoulder.
Click on the virtual measurement line, then click on the delete button on the keyboard.
Activate the simulation.
The 3D tool bar will move and stick to the internal самой.
Then click on the 3D tool bar, click on the 3D tool bar, and then click on the 3D movement.
When you click on the 3D tool bar, the 3D model will change.
The 3D model will move and stick to the internal
Draw a 3D model.
The CAD model will move.
Cards can be selected by clicking on the T-shirt.